Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every
wall that's in our wake!
Go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing that
surely someday we just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards
a bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up. Way up high.
Always step up.
If waves erupt up to the sky.
Never give up. Our wishes.
They will come together.
And lead us on.
For the future.
We drift on.
Riding the waves.
Towards another shore.
Day by day.
There are many meetings.
Many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember.
The pain within, I'll keep
it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly,
but I won't surrender.
This freedom, I will keep in mind,
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up,
sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up, raise up
the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up, we'll get past
everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up when I'm high.
Always step up, if waves are
rough, jump through the sky.
Never give up, our wishes
they will come together.
And lead us on towards our future.
Hands up.
I've worn that thing with
some kind of passive beast.
But when the hell has
Caesar ever been interested?
in human weapons?
Get me in range!
Coming right up!
Whatever it is, he'll
regret shooting at us.
If you wanted to fight, well here it is!
General, and okay!
I didn't even put a dent in him!
General! Shield!
That's too little and too late!
General!
Shield!
Thread through a shield?
Talk about desperate!
Well, then.
Looks like I'm just gonna have
to break out the big guns.
Sorry, pal.
As long as you're standing
between us and Caesar,
I'm afraid that makes you our enemy.
Weapon Morphosis!
Esparagirl!
Good guy!
Round and round!
Shut up!
What were you saying about
no more getting sidetracked?
Time for a more direct approach.
Call me Missile Girl.
Target is inside!
Ready, fire!
Launching! Spin!
Projecto Cannon!
Caesar's coming with us!
Wait, Caesar?
What are you even talking about?
Where the hell am I?
the heart of the leader
of the g5 what a wonderful
souvenir thanks with
this the fight is over
Smoker, your heart is still in my
hands, and I'm not going to hell alone.
What the hell are you Straw Hats
standing around and waiting for?
We can't let Caesar escape, or the
entire plan will be for nothing.
All of you, get on now!
Sure we will, when we have everyone.
I'm waiting for my whole crew!
Run like your life depends on it!
We're trying the best we can, Usopp!
You gotta move faster than the gas!
Hooray!
The gate is starting to close!
Only 50 meters left,
then you're home free!
We're going with you!
Whatever floats your boat!
The gate's gonna close!
They're here!
That was a close call!
The crew's all here!
Were you trying to make us worry?
I knew you'd make it!
It was all thanks to
you, Usa! That's right!
We didn't see him carrying you!
Well, guys, you heard him!
No reason to wait around,
right? All aboard!
Time to get out of here! Yeah!
what about Kin'emon is there anything
we can do for him what that's Kin'emon
we're just gonna have to figure something
out later no what do they do to you
Joker, are you there?
Me.
Monet.
Monet?
I'm surprised you're alive.
Vargo's been defeated.
Caesar as well.
Though Baby Five and Buffalo
should be able to recover him soon.
I misjudged the whole situation.
Deep in the third lab,
you'll find the weapon responsible for
destroying the first two laboratories,
as well as the rest of the
island, exactly four years ago.
With the simple push of a button,
Punk Hazard's population will
be reduced to a single person.
The only one who can survive
the land of the dead.
Our dear friend Caesar.
The location of the device...
You don't need to say another word, Joker.
I was going to do it anyway.
Actually, I'm next to
the switch right now.
The explosion will sink
their only means of escape.
Just as long as you're
okay with losing a tanker.
Very good.
die for me.
Monda and take everything with you.
young master.
at the very least.
I'll get my revenge on you.
this is goodbye!
I, sorry it had to end
like this, old friend.
Thank you, for your years of service.
Pretty hot, huh, this Missile
Girl's burning passion.
Hey, hey, baby, fly!
You still want to hold on to this weapon?
I mean, you can already turn
into every weapon you want.
Thanks for grabbing it, Buffalo.
That was sweet, that weapons
imbued with magic powers, you know.
Whoever owns this weapon is
bound to lead a happy life,
and if you buy it from me,
you'll make me a happy man, too.
That was just a scam obviously,
oh crap!
Look up behind you, baby!
Oh, Iron Pirate! Wow!
I don't fight for peace on the sea!
Is that even for me?
No!
Iron Pirate!
Done with this.
Weapon-morphosis!
Revolver girl!
Ha! That's it!
This ought to do the job.
Deflect this!
Why is there a dragon here with us?
Momo, I made him out of
garbage dump. Wow, what?
Father!
This eel is quite distraught.
Please save my father!
It's gone mad!
Momo, what's wrong?
Every one of you, this is where
you will die here with me,
though I won't be around to see it.
I know you'll become
the king of the pirates!
Hey, are you okay?
I don't know what happened.
But that sounded pretty bad.
Must have come from building D.
Trust me, I know.
That's the S .A .D.
Manufacturing Room.
Monet!
Hey, hello.
I was under the impression that my
heart was in Caesar's possession.
So how the hell did you end
up getting your hands on it?
Simply put, he got
mixed up on the details.
I hold on to your heart for safekeeping.
He let me hold on to his
secretary Monet's heart.
We have ourselves a deal,
shall we shake on it?
And as you know, I sliced out your
heart when you first arrived at the lab.
The heart of the leader of
the T5, Vice Admiral Smoker.
What a wonderful souvenir.
Thanks.
He just made that assumption and
I didn't bother correcting him.
But I gave him back Monet's
heart out of kindness.
I need a response.
As the old saying goes, when you do
something nice for other people...
Well, that good karma's
bound to come back to you.
Oh, crap!
This tunnel's gonna collapse any second!
I got it!
The ceiling's completely giving out!
This tunnel is burrowed
directly through the mountains.
The cave Zin will be buried.
You gotta do something about it or what?
Damn it!
The passage is blocked!
Hit the brakes!
Holy crap!
He saved us!
I don't want that guy as
my enemy, even if he is!
There's bound to be a gas
cloud blocking the exit.
Anyone on board capable of
conjuring up some wind? What?
You expect someone to just
coincidentally have that power?
Oh, right here.
I can do that. Seriously?
I can see the end of the tunnel!
Nice.
Just a little more to go.
Move faster!
Where are you?
I can't find the young master.
He should be in his room
on the fourth floor.
But he's not.
I looked up there.
The window was open.
Ah, well then.
I don't know where he is.
Sounds like he headed
off on his own again.
It's me.
Tell me what's happening over there.
Actually.
We got some kind of metal security guard.
Giving us trouble.
But other than that.
The two of you are still safe.
Yes sir.
All right, it's settled.
For now, I want you two to
take care of that guard.
I'll be there shortly.
Huh?
I am an Invincible Iron Palace!
Super!
After an attack like that, even
a pacifista would be busted up.
Weapon Morphosis!
Flying Sis Girl!
Make his head spin!
Weapon Morphosis!
Fire Girl!
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
No enemy, however strong,
is immune from the burning passion
of Firegirl's flame of love.
Fix that, Franky.
General AMG!
What?
Any fresh ideas?
He's one tough customer.
Bring it on!
I'm ready for more, fan
man and weapon woman!
Hey, baby, you think what I'm thinking?
We serve him up something special
that no one's ever been able to block.
Try your best.
It won't matter.
Super!
Nothing will work.
We'll chop you up down to nuts and bolts.
Behold the spinning weapon of death.
Sickle girl, go!
Okay, I'll give you props.
It's not every day
someone's got enough power
to punch a hole through the general body.
But I gotta say, what you're trying to do,
it's like a praying man that's
looking to sink a battleship.
You're in for a treat, the thousand
sun will come in a whole sea one day,
but in the.
In the meantime, I want
to give you a taste.
of this ultimate secret weapon.
Don't tell anybody else
though, cause it's a secret.
The land-based portal gallon cannon.
The working title is...
Take it!
Shenron King!
Still don't know who this guy is!
Or why he's so hell-bent on
keeping up from retrieving Caesar!
Who's that passed out down there?
Looks like Caesar.
Wonder how he got all the way out here.
It don't matter who's paying you.
We're not gonna get our
asses kicked that easily.
Well, well.
Still standing, huh?
Gotta admit you're tough, for real.
If you think we're just your
garden-variety hooligans,
pal, you're gonna get a rude awakening!
We swear!
By the name of Joker!
We're taking Caesar! You hear me?
You won't stop us!
Ah!
So your plan is finally revealed!
You guys are trying to escape with Caesar!
I see a light up ahead!
Keep the wind going, Nami! More!
It's gonna be a world of poison outside!
You've seen what I've seen!
The general's so cool! What?
Super!
It's a super!
With a good toy!
Buffalo.
Baby Five, what are you doing here? Us?
And what do you think you're doing
helping the Straw Hats and kids escape?
Because Lost turned traitor.
Joker saved the heart seed for
you, and you go and betray him!
Wait, are they your friends or something?
Negative.
They're my enemies.
All of the Straw Hats in the
Navy Team Five against us?
Those are losing odds.
We gotta split!
Wait, Baby Five, what's going on?
Why are you here? Saving you.
We're taking you to the young master.
They grabbed Caesar and made a run for it.
You know what that means.
It's a sniper's job to take him down.
Those bastards...
Hold up, Law.
Usopp said he's got a handle
on the situation, didn't he?
First class sniper.
Don't underestimate him.
You're crazy.
What if he misses?
If Caesar escapes, this
whole planet's ruined.
Are we in alliance or aren't we?
If we're going to work together,
how about showing a little trust?
What alliance? Hang on.
Don't think so.
I'm done waiting.
I went on the offense.
Think you got away?
Think again, cowards!
You're all going down!
That's right!
Especially when they're wounded
and their backs are to us!
Too easy!
Yeah, any day.
First, you need a little water.
Now, work your magic!
It's time to grow!
Black Kabuto and... Chump grass!
Eat up!
You're gonna need it!
It looks like they're about to attack.
Be careful, buffalo—leave the
flag to me while I'm busy.
You keep the skies clear.
We got a mission to complete.
What, Roger?
That, my—you really
need me. Don't you then?
I'll be there.
I'll protect you with my life.
Go, high feather egg!
feather egg
Something just flew overhead!
Time to hatch!
Little bolt!
A thunder storm? Buffalo!
We gotta go!
I'm trying, I'm trying!
Oh no, not so fast.
Meteorology attack!
Thunderbreed!
No way! Tempo! Stop!
Say something, baby! Damn it!
She's out cold!
Time to wrap this up!
Do it, Jumpgrass!
Special attack!
Meteor Storm Assault!
Buffalo!
I can't move!
Or fly for that matter!
Please, you gotta protect me!
I always perform my duty!
I'm part of the Dachyote family!
The mission above all else!
Lights, idiot!
You're good for nothing!
Go on, try it! I'm gas!
You can't hit me.
Gotta make it to Dressrosa with or without
Buffalo and Baby Five. Nope. Afraid not.
That last shot.
No. What is this?
A sea prism stone handcuff.
And that is how it's done.
Yeah, in your face, Caesar.
When the enemy turns
their back, I'm there.
With the enemy?
Yeah, we get it.
Fine.
Looks like the initial
phase is accomplished.
Told you.
Pretty strong, aren't they?
looks like i overslept no big deal
now then which way is punk hazard